{
    "subject": "Peter_III_of_Russia",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Catherine_II_of_Russia",
    "human_readable": "Peter III of Russia is married to Catherine II of Russia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9666219353675842,
            "question": "Who was married to Peter III of Russia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9559996128082275,
            "question": "To whom was Catherine II of Russia married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9525081515312195,
            "question": "What was significant about the marriage of Peter III and Catherine II in Russian history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9313498735427856,
            "question": "Who were the spouses of Peter III and Catherine II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9287956953048706,
            "question": "Was Catherine II of Russia married to a Russian ruler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8882800936698914,
            "question": "What was the name of Peter III of Russia's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8463619351387024,
            "question": "Did Peter III and Catherine II rule Russia together?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7797411680221558,
            "question": "Were there any political implications to the marriage between Peter III and Catherine II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6893882751464844,
            "question": "What was the nature of the relationship between Peter III and Catherine II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5706213116645813,
            "question": "Were Peter III and Catherine II romantically involved?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Peter III of Russia is married to Catherine II of Russia.",
            "html": "yago_27852_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the nature of the relationship between Peter III and Catherine II?",
            "html": "yago_27852_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any political implications to the marriage between Peter III and Catherine II?",
            "html": "yago_27852_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Peter III and Catherine II rule Russia together?",
            "html": "yago_27852_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27852_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27852_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27852_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27852_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27852_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27852_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27852_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27852_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27852_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27852_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text documents explicitly state that Peter III and Catherine II were married.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information about the marriage and reign of Catherine II (also known as Catherine the Great) and her husband Peter III, which supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Peter III of Russia is married to Catherine II of Russia.\" Multiple sources confirm their marriage in 1745, and it is described as a political arrangement for her to marry Peter III, who was in line to the Russian throne."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}